<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learn Loop</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">496379855971971</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1234</string>
    <string name="facebook_client_token">56789</string>

    <string name="app_description1">The app aims to promote the genuine adoption of financial literacy knowledge taught in schools during Education &amp; Career Guidance modules.</string>
    <string name="app_description2">Even though students are exposed to basic financial literacy concepts such as “Budgeting”, youths do not put it into practice as the modules only provide theoretical knowledge, not practical knowledge.</string>
    <string name="app_description3">LearnLoop aims to provide the practical knowledge aspect through features such as:\n ⚪ Setting Budgets\n ⚪ Budgeting\n ⚪ Expenditure Tracker\n ⚪ Financial Literacy Courses\n ⚪ Student Discount Library</string>

    <string name="smu_title">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</string>
    <string name="smu_name">Singapore Management University</string>
    <string name="smu_subname">Sim Kee Boon Institute for Financial Economics</string>

    <string name="course1_title">Budgeting Principles</string>
    <string name="course1_lecturer">Kang Thet Sing</string>
    <string name="course1_lecturerpos">Senior Lecturer at SP</string>

    <string name="smu_desc">In a competitive landscape where money often has the final word, there is a pressing need for young adults to learn about taking control of their finances. Many will want to start planning a roadmap to financial success. This is where the program aims to help answer the million-dollar question: how to stay the course and build lifelong wealth?\n\nAll of the essentials are included in this world-ready program. These...</string>


    <string name="budgeting_principles_desc">Making a budgeting plan is one thing. Sticking to it is another.\n\nThis course focuses on refreshing your budgeting knowledge acquired from school such as concepts, plans, identifying and classification of expenditures and more.\n\nThis course will also guide you on building a sustainable budgeting plan and share tips on how one can stick to the plan in the long r...</string>

    <string-array name="transaction_title">
        <item name="Potato">Potato Corners</item>
        <item name="Payback">Pay back to Thet Pine</item>
        <item name="BlackPanther">Black Panther Movie</item>
        <item name="Yakiniku">Yakiniku Return</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="transaction_purpose">
        <item name="foodndrinks">FOOD AND DRINKS</item>
        <item name="transfer">BANK TRANSFER</item>
        <item name="ENTERTAINMENT">ENTERTAINMENT</item>
        <item name="transfer">BANK TRANSFER</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="transaction_amount">
        <item name="-13.20">-$13.20</item>
        <item name="-4.50">-$4.50</item>
        <item name="-$8.50">-$8.50</item>
        <item name="+$12.90">+$12.90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_title">
        <item name="Financial Market">20 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">21 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">22 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">23 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">24 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">25 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">26 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">27 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">28 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">29 December 2022</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_host">
        <item name="Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</item>
        <item name="-4.50">-$4.50</item>
        <item name="-$8.50">-$8.50</item>
        <item name="+$12.90">+$12.90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="host_desc">
        <item name="Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</item>
        <item name="-4.50">-$4.50</item>
        <item name="-$8.50">-$8.50</item>
        <item name="+$12.90">+$12.90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_participants">
        <item name="Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</item>
        <item name="-4.50">-$4.50</item>
        <item name="-$8.50">-$8.50</item>
        <item name="+$12.90">+$12.90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_title">
        <item name="Financial Market">Introduction to Financial Markets</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">Introduction to Finance and Accounting</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">Investment and Portfolio Management</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">Finance &amp; Quantitatie Modelling for Analysts</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">Finance for Non-Finance Professionals</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">Behavioral Finance</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">Business and Financial Modelling</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">Fundamentals of Finance</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">Cost Accounting</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_host">
        <item name="Financial Market">Robert Shiller</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">Brian J Bushee</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">Arzu Ozoguz</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">Michael R Roberts</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">James Weston</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">Emma Rasiel</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">Sergei Savin</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">Marla Noel</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">Xuhu Wan</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">Gunther Friedl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="courseHost_Desc">
        <item name="Financial Market">Professor of Economics, Yale University</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">The Geoffrey T. Boisi Professor</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">Finance Faculty</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">Professor of Finance, University of Pennsylvania</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">Harmon Whittington Professor of Finance</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">Associate Chair and Professor</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">Associate Professor of Operations, Information and Decisions</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">UCI Division of Continuing Education Instructor</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">Associate Professor</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">Prof. Dr.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_duration">
        <item name="Financial Market">34 hours</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">5 months</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">6 months</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">4 months</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">14 hours</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">5 hours</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">6 months</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">10 hours</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">13 hours</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">3 months</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_lesson">
        <item name="Financial Market">7 modules</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">4 courses</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">5 courses</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">4 courses</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">5 modules</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">3 modules</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">5 courses</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">4 modules</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">4 modules</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">3 courses</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_desc">
        <item name="Financial Market">An overview of the ideas, methods, and institutions that permit human society to manage risks and foster enterprise.  Emphasis on financially-savvy leadership skills. Description of practices today and analysis of prospects for the future. Introduction to risk management and behavioral finance principles to understand the real-world functioning of securities, insurance, and banking industries.  The ultimate goal of this course is using such industries effectively and towards a better society.</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">This specialization provides an introduction to corporate finance and accounting, emphasizing their application to a wide variety of real-world situations spanning personal finance, corporate decision-making, financial intermediation, and how accounting standards and managerial incentives affect the financial reporting process. It begins with concepts and applications like time value of money, risk-return tradeoff, retirement savings, mortgage financing, auto leasing, asset valuation, and many others.  The specialization uses Excel to make the experience more hands-on and help learners understand the concepts more directly.  From valuing claims and making financing decisions, to elements of a basic financial model, the coursework provides a solid foundation to corporate finance. The specialization then moves to financial accounting, enabling learners to read financial statements and to understand the language and grammar of accounting.  The coursework introduces bookkeeping fundamentals, accrual accounting, cash flow analysis, among much else!  Finally, using the foundational knowledge of accounting, the specialization teaches learners how to understand and analyze key information that companies provide in their statements, including types of assets and liabilities and longer-term investments and debts, and finally the difference between tax reporting and financial reporting.</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">In this four-course Specialization, you’ll learn the essential skills of portfolio management and personal investing. All investors – from the largest wealth funds to the smallest individual investors – share common issues in investing: how to meet their liabilities, how to decide where to invest, and how much risk to take on. In this Specialization, you will learn how to think about, discuss, and formulate solutions to these investment questions. You will learn the theory and the real-world skills necessary to design, execute, and evaluate investment proposals that meet financial objectives. You will begin with an overview of global financial markets and instruments that characterize the investment opportunities available to today’s investor. You will then learn how to construct optimal portfolios that manage risk effectively, and how to capitalize on understanding behavioral biases and irrational behavior in financial markets. You will learn the best practices in portfolio management and performance evaluation as well as current investment strategies. By the end of your Capstone Project, you will have mastered the analytical tools, quantitative skills, and practical knowledge necessary for long-term investment management success.</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">The role of an Analyst is dynamic, complex, and driven by a variety of skills. These skills range from a basic understanding of financial statement data and non-financial metrics that can be linked to financial performance, to a deeper dive into business and financial modeling. Analysts also utilize spreadsheet models, modeling techniques, and common investment analysis application as part of their toolkit to make informed financial decisions and investments. This multifaceted specialization will equip a learner who might be interested in entering the dynamic world of data and business analysis, and/or is interested gaining deeper technical knowledge in Finance and Quantitative Modeling. Starting from the fundamentals of quantitative modeling, you will learn how to put data to work by using spreadsheets and leverage spreadsheets as a powerful, accessible data analysis tool. You will also be introduced to the world of corporate finance, and gain a better understanding of finance fundamentals, including a variety of real-world situations spanning personal finance, corporate decision-making and financial intermediation.</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">This short course surveys all the major topics covered in a full semester MBA level finance course, but with a more intuitive approach on a very high conceptual level.  The goal here is give you a roadmap and framework for how financial professional make decisions. We will cover the basics of financial valuation, the time value of money, compounding returns, and discounting the future.  You will understand discounted cash flow (DCF) valuation and how it compares to other methods.  We also step inside the mind of a corporate financial manager and develop the basic tools of capital budgeting.  We will survey the how, when, and where to spend money, make tradeoffs about investment, growth, dividends, and how to ensure sound fiscal discipline.  Our journey then turns to a Wall Street or capital markets perspective of investments as we discuss the fundamental tradeoff between risk and return.  We then synthesize our discussion of risk with our valuation framework and incorporate it into series of direct applications to practice. This course requires no prior familiarity with finance.  Rather, it is intended to be a first step for anyone who is curious about understanding stock markets, valuation, or corporate finance.  We will walk through all of the tools and quantitative analysis together and develop a guide for understanding the seemingly complex decisions that finance professionals make. By the end of the course, you will develop an understanding of the major conceptual levers that push and pull on financial decision making and how they relate to other areas of business.  The course should also serve as a roadmap for where to further your finance education and it would be an excellent introduction of any students contemplating an MBA or Finance concentration, but who has little background in the area.</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">We make thousands of decisions every day. Do I cross the road now, or wait for the oncoming truck to pass? Should I eat fries or a salad for lunch? How much should I tip the cab driver? We usually make these decisions with almost no thought, using what psychologists call “heuristics” – rules of thumb that enable us to navigate our lives. Without these mental shortcuts, we would be paralyzed by the multitude of daily choices. But in certain circumstances, these shortcuts lead to predictable errors – predictable, that is, if we know what to watch out for. Did you know, for example, that we are naturally biased towards selling investments that are doing well for us, but holding on to those that are doing poorly? Or that we often select sub-optimal insurance payment plans, and routinely purchase insurance that we don’t even need? And why do so many of us fail to enroll in our employer’s corporate retirement plans, even when the employer offers to match our contributions? Behavioral finance is the study of these and dozens of other financial decision-making errors that can be avoided, if we are familiar with the biases that cause them. In this course, we examine these predictable errors, and discover where we are most susceptible to them. This course is intended to guide participants towards better financial choices. Learn how to improve your spending, saving, and investing decisions for the future.</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">Wharton\'s Business and Financial Modeling Specialization is designed to help you make informed business and financial decisions. These foundational courses will introduce you to spreadsheet models, modeling techniques, and common applications for investment analysis, company valuation, forecasting, and more. When you complete the Specialization, you\'ll be ready to use your own data to describe realities, build scenarios, and predict performance. </item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">Welcome to Fundamentals of Finance. This 4 module course will help you understand and affect the performance of your unit or organization’s profitability. By the end of this course, you will be able to implement finance and accounting concepts to drive your organization\'s growth, analyze financial statements and understand the factors in productivity and profitability, and create forecasting and budgeting. You will also have the ability to evaluate and manage cash flow, implement strategies around financing, and use of ratios in running a business.</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">Course Overview: https://youtu.be/JgFV5qzAYno Python is now becoming the number 1 programming language for data science. Due to python’s simplicity and high readability, it is gaining its importance in the financial industry.  The course combines both python coding and statistical concepts and applies into analyzing financial data, such as stock data. By the end of the course, you can achieve the following using python: \n\n- Import, pre-process, save and visualize financial data into pandas Dataframe \n\n- Manipulate the existing financial data by generating new variables using multiple columns \n\n- Recall and apply the important statistical concepts (random variable, frequency, distribution, population and sample, confidence interval, linear regression, etc. ) into financial contexts \n\n- Build a trading model using multiple linear regression model \n\n- Evaluate the performance of the trading model using different investment indicators \n\nJupyter Notebook environment is configured in the course platform for practicing python coding without installing any client applications.</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">View the Specialization trailer: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XE5Rx91bdYw \n\nMany corporate decisions need cost accounting information. When you know the costs of your products, you will make better pricing decisions and you can better choose which products to offer. When you know the costs of your departments, you can better detect inefficiencies and you can better incentivize your employees. \n\nIn this Specialization, you will learn the fundamentals of cost accounting. Three courses cover the basics of cost accounting. We will start with an introduction to product costing. How can you figure out the costs of your individual products? Next, we will discuss how to connect cost information with revenue information to calculate profits and profitability. Finally, we focus on how to use the information provided by cost accounting systems to optimize your business decisions. \n\nWe have created the courses of this Specialization for interdisciplinary young professionals seeking to develop cost accounting skills. At the same time, the courses can help students in management and business administration to repeat the content of their introductory cost accounting course.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_university">
        <item name="Financial Market">Yale University</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">University of Pennsylvania</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">Rice University</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">Rice University</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">Rice University</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">Duke University</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">University of Pennsylvania</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">University of California, Irvine</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">Technische Universitat Munchen (TUM)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_universityDesc">
        <item name="Financial Market">7 modules</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">4 courses</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">5 courses</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">4 courses</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">5 modules</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">3 modules</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">5 courses</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">4 modules</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">4 modules</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">3 courses</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_publishedDates">
        <item name="Financial Market">20 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">21 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">22 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">23 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">24 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">25 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">26 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">27 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">28 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">29 December 2022</item>
    </string-array>




</resources>

    <!--    Even though students are exposed to basic financial literacy concepts such as “Budgeting”, youths do not put it into practice as the modules only provide theoretical knowledge, not practical knowledge.-->

    <!--    LearnLoop aims to provide the practical knowledge aspect through features such as:\n ⚪ Setting Budgets\n ⚪ Budgeting\n ⚪ Expenditure Tracker\n ⚪ Financial Literacy Courses\n ⚪ Student Discount Library-->