<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learn Loop</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="facebook_app_id">496379855971971</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1234</string>
    <string name="facebook_client_token">56789</string>

    <string name="app_description1">The app aims to promote the genuine adoption of financial literacy knowledge taught in schools during Education &amp; Career Guidance modules.</string>
    <string name="app_description2">Even though students are exposed to basic financial literacy concepts such as “Budgeting”, youths do not put it into practice as the modules only provide theoretical knowledge, not practical knowledge.</string>
    <string name="app_description3">LearnLoop aims to provide the practical knowledge aspect through features such as:\n ⚪ Setting Budgets\n ⚪ Budgeting\n ⚪ Expenditure Tracker\n ⚪ Financial Literacy Courses\n ⚪ Student Discount Library</string>

    <string name="smu_title">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</string>
    <string name="smu_name">Singapore Management University</string>
    <string name="smu_subname">Sim Kee Boon Institute for Financial Economics</string>

    <string name="course1_title">Budgeting Principles</string>
    <string name="course1_lecturer">Kang Thet Sing</string>
    <string name="course1_lecturerpos">Senior Lecturer at SP</string>
    

    <string name="smu_desc">In a competitive landscape where money often has the final word, there is a pressing need for young adults to learn about taking control of their finances. Many will want to start planning a roadmap to financial success. This is where the program aims to help answer the million-dollar question: how to stay the course and build lifelong wealth?\n\nAll of the essentials are included in this world-ready program. These...</string>


    <string name="budgeting_principles_desc">Making a budgeting plan is one thing. Sticking to it is another.\n\nThis course focuses on refreshing your budgeting knowledge acquired from school such as concepts, plans, identifying and classification of expenditures and more.\n\nThis course will also guide you on building a sustainable budgeting plan and share tips on how one can stick to the plan in the long r...</string>

    <!-- Your account -->
    <string name="Your_account">See information about your account, download an archive of your data, or learn about your account deactivation options.</string>

    <!-- Security and account access -->
    <string name="security_and_account">Manage your account\'s security and keep track of your account\'s usage including apps that you have connected to your account</string>

    <!-- Privacy and safety -->
    <string name="privacy_and_safety">Manage what information you see and share on Twitter.</string>

    <!-- Notifications -->
    <string name="notifications">Select the kinds of notifications you get about your activities, interest, and recommendations.</string>

    <!-- Accessibility, display, and language -->
    <string name="accessibility">Manage how SPACED content is displayed to you.</string>

    <!-- Additional resources -->
    <string name="Additional_resources">Check out other places for helpful information to learn more about SPACED products and services.</string>

    <!-- Your account description -->
    <string name="YourAccount_description">See information about your account, download an archive of your data, or learn about your account deactivation options.</string>

    <!-- Account information -->
    <string name="accInfo">See information about your account, download an archive of your data, or learn about your account deactivation options.</string>

    <!-- Change Password -->
    <string name="changePassword">Change your password at any time.</string>

    <!-- Download an archive of your data -->
    <string name="dataArchive">Get insights into the type of information stored for your account.</string>

    <!-- Deactivate account -->
    <string name="deactivateAcc">Find out how you can deactivate your account.</string>

    <!-- Security and account access description -->
    <string name="security_account_access_description">Manage your account\'s security and keep track of your account\'s usage including apps that you have connected to your account.</string>

    <!-- Security -->
    <string name="security">Manage your account\'s security</string>

    <!-- Apps and session -->
    <string name="apps_and_session">See information about when you logged into your account and the apps you connected to your account.</string>

    <!-- Connected accounts -->
    <string name="connectedAcc">Manage Google or Apple accounts connected to SPACED to log in.</string>

    <!-- Ads preference -->
    <string name="adsPreference">Manage your ads experience on LearnLoop.</string>

    <!-- Off-SPACED activity -->
    <string name="off_spaced_activity">Manage how LearnLoop uses your online activity outside of it, such as the website you visit, to personalize your experience.</string>

    <!-- Data sharing with business partner -->
    <string name="dataSharing">Allow sharing of additional information with LearnLoop\'s business partners.</string>

    <!-- Location information -->
    <string name="locationInfo">Manage the location information LearnLoop uses to personalize your experience.</string>

    <!-- Notification description -->
    <string name="notificationDesc">Select the kind of notifications you get about your activities, interests, and recommendations.</string>

    <!-- Filters -->
    <string name="filters">Choose the notifications you will like to see-and those you don\'t</string>

    <!-- Preferences -->
    <string name="preferences">Select your preferences by notification type.</string>

    <!-- Accessibility, display, languages description-->
    <string name="accessibility_display_language_description">Manage how LearnLoop content is displayed to you.</string>

    <!-- Accessibility -->
    <string name="Accessibility">Manage aspects of your LearnLoop experience such as limiting color contrast and motion. These settings affect all the LearnLoop accounts on the device.</string>

    <!-- Display and sound -->
    <string name="display_and_sound">Manage your font size, color and background.These settings affect all of LearnLoops accounts on this device.</string>

    <!-- Languages -->
    <string name="Languages">Manage which languages are used to personalize your LearnLoop experience.</string>

    <!-- Data usage -->
    <string name="dataUsage">Limit how LearnLoop uses some of your network data. These settings affect all the LearnLoop accounts on this device.</string>

    <!-- Deactivation text -->
    <string name="txtAccDeactivation">You\'re about to start the process of deactivating your SPACED account. Your display name, @username, and profile will no longer be viewable on SPACED.com, SPACED for iOS, or SPACED for Android.</string>

    <!-- What else you should know -->
    <string name="WhatElseToKnow">You can restore your SPACED account if it was accidentally or wrongfully deactivated for up to 30days after deactivation. \n \nSome account information may still be available in search engines, such as Google or Bing. \n \nIf you just want to change your @username, you don\'t need to deactivate your account - edit it in your settings. \n \nTo use your current @username or email address with a different SPACED account, change them before you deactivate this account. \n \nIf you want to download your SPACED data, you\'ll need to complete both the request and download process before deactivating your account. Links to download your data cannot be sent to deactivate accounts.</string>

    <!-- Two-factor authentication-->
    <string name="two_factor_authentication">Protect your account from unauthorized access by requiring a second authentication method in addition to your SPACED password. You can choose text message, authentication app, or security key.</string>

    <!-- Password reset protection -->
    <string name="passwordProtection">For added protection, you\'ll need to confirm your email address or phone number to reset your SPACED password.</string>

    <!-- Ads preference -->
    <string name="adsPreference_description">You will always see ads on SPACED based on your activity. When this setting is enabled, SPACED may further personalize ads from SPACED advertisers, on and off SPACED, by combining your activity with other online activity and information from our partners.</string>

    <!-- SPACED content across web -->
    <string name="SPACED_content_across_web">This setting lets SPACED keep track of your visits to other websites that integrate SPACED content, such as embedded timelines. That information makes SPACED better for you, such as by personalizing your experience. This web browsing history will never be stored with your name email, or phone number.</string>

    <!-- Personalized identity -->
    <string name="personalizedIdentity">SPACED will always personalize your experience based on information you\'ve provided, as well as the devices you\'ve used to log in. When this setting is enabled, SPACED may also personalize based on other inferences about your identity, like devices and browsers you haven\'t used to log in to SPACED or email addresses and phone numbers similar to those linked to your SPACED account.</string>

    <!-- Off-SPACED activity -->
    <string name="off_SPACED_description">Manage how SPACED uses your online activity outside of SPACED, such as the websites you visit, to personalize your experience.</string>

    <!-- Information sharing -->
    <string name="infoSharing">SPACED always shares information with business partners as a way to run and improve its products. When enabled, this allows SPACED to share additional information with those partners to help support running SPACED\'s business, including making SPACED\'s marketing activities on other sites and apps more relevant for you.</string>

    <!-- Personalize location -->
    <string name="personalizeLocation">SPACED always uses some information, like where you signed up and your current location, to help show you more relevant content. When this setting is enabled, SPACED may also personalize your experiences - for example, showing you more local content, ads, and recommendations.</string>

    <!-- Precise location -->
    <string name="preciseLocation">If enabled, SPACED will collect, store, and user your device\'s precise location, such as GPS information. This lets SPACED improve your experience-for example, showing you more local content, ads, and recommendations.</string>

    <!-- Privacy policy intro -->
    <string name="privacyPolicyIntro">Last update: 03/7/22 \n\n This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the app.\n\nWe use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.</string>

    <!-- Log data -->
    <string name="logData">Like many app operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our App.\n\n This Log Data may include information such as your computer\'s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our app that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.</string>

    <!-- Communication -->
    <string name="communication">We will not use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletter, marketing or promotional materials and other information. We will only be contacting you through email with regards to new updates of the app and replies to our user\'s feedback.</string>

    <!-- Information collection and use -->
    <string name="infoCollection">While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information will include your name, contact information.</string>

    <!-- Security -->
    <string name="privacyPolicy_security">The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.</string>

    <!-- Changes to privacy policy -->
    <string name="privacyPolicy_changes">This Privacy Policy is effective as of (add date) and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.\n\nWe reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.\n\n If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our app.</string>

    <!-- Accessibility -->
    <string name="Accessibility_desc">Manage aspects of your SPACED experience such as limiting color contrast and motion. These settings affect all the SPACED accounts on this device.</string>

    <!-- Reduce motion -->
    <string name="reduceMotion">Limits the amount of in-app animations, including screen transitions and live engagement counts.</string>

    <!-- Reader view -->
    <string name="readerView">Change text size, contrast, and page layout on website for improved readability.</string>

    <!-- Display and sound description -->
    <string name="display_and_sound_desc">Manage your font size, color and background. These settings affect all the SPACED accounts on this device.</string>

    <!-- Display and sound description -->
    <string name="display_sound_desc">Manage your font size, color and background. These settings affect all the SPACED accounts on this device.</string>

    <!-- Display text demo -->
    <string name="displayDemo">At the hear of SPACED are short messages called SPACEDTweets - just like this one - which can include photos, videos, links and text.</string>

    <!-- Recommendations -->
    <string name="recommendations">Select which languages you want text, people, and trends to include.</string>

    <!-- Data usage -->
    <string name="dataUsage_desc">limit how SPACED uses some of your network data. These settings affect all the SPACED accounts on this device.</string>

    <!-- Data saver -->
    <string name="dataSaver">When enabled, videos won\'t autoplay and lower-quality images load. This automatically reduces your data usage for all SPACED accounts on this device.</string>

    <!-- Legal notice -->
    <string name="legalNotice">Copyright © 2022–2031 P.Thet Pine. All rights reserved.\n\nCreated and based partly on code by P. Thet Pine on 4/7/22. \n\nPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files, to deal in the Software without restriction,including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions: \n\nThe above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software. \n\nAny person wishing to distribute modifications to the Software is asked to send the modifications to the original developer so that they can be incorporated into the canonical version. This is, however, not a binding provision of this license. \n\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED [AS IF], WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</string>

    <!-- Authentication app -->
    <string name="authenticationApp">Use an app to get an authentication code to enter when you log in to SPACED.</string>

    <!-- Security key -->
    <string name="securityKey">Use a security key that inserts into your computer or syncs to your mobile device when you log in to SPACED. You\'ll need to use a supported mobile device or web browser.</string>

    <!-- Quality filter  -->
    <string name="qualityFilter">Filter lower-quality content from your notifications. This won\'t filter out notifications from people you follow or accounts you\'ve interacted with recently.</string>

    <!-- Email notification -->
    <string name="emailNotification_desc">Get emails to find out what\'s going on when you\'re not on SPACED. You can turn them off anytime.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="transaction_title">
        <item name="Potato">Potato Corners</item>
        <item name="Payback">Pay back to Thet Pine</item>
        <item name="BlackPanther">Black Panther Movie</item>
        <item name="Yakiniku">Yakiniku Return</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="transaction_purpose">
        <item name="foodndrinks">FOOD AND DRINKS</item>
        <item name="transfer">BANK TRANSFER</item>
        <item name="ENTERTAINMENT">ENTERTAINMENT</item>
        <item name="transfer">BANK TRANSFER</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="transaction_amount">
        <item name="-13.20">-$13.20</item>
        <item name="-4.50">-$4.50</item>
        <item name="-$8.50">-$8.50</item>
        <item name="+$12.90">+$12.90</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_title">
        <item name="smu">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</item>
        <item name="smu">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</item>
        <item name="smu">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</item>
        <item name="smu">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</item>
        <item name="smu">Citi Foundation-SMU Financial Literacy Program for Young Adults</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_host">
        <item name="smu">Singapore Management University</item>
        <item name="smu">Singapore Management University</item>
        <item name="smu">Singapore Management University</item>
        <item name="smu">Singapore Management University</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="host_desc">
        <item name="smu">Sim Kee Boon Institute for Financial Economics</item>
        <item name="smu">Sim Kee Boon Institute for Financial Economics</item>
        <item name="smu">Sim Kee Boon Institute for Financial Economics</item>
        <item name="smu">Sim Kee Boon Institute for Financial Economics</item>
        <item name="smu">Sim Kee Boon Institute for Financial Economics</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_participants">
        <item name="smu">1,200+ Participants</item>
        <item name="smu">1,200+ Participants</item>
        <item name="smu">1,200+ Participants</item>
        <item name="smu">1,200+ Participants</item>
        <item name="smu">1,200+ Participants</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="event_link">
        <item name="smu">https://skbi.smu.edu.sg/cfs</item>
        <item name="smu">https://skbi.smu.edu.sg/cfs</item>
        <item name="smu">https://skbi.smu.edu.sg/cfs</item>
        <item name="smu">https://skbi.smu.edu.sg/cfs</item>
        <item name="smu">https://skbi.smu.edu.sg/cfs</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_link">
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/learn/financial-markets-global</item>
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/specializations/finance-accounting</item>
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/specializations/investment-portolio-management</item>
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/specializations/finance-quantitative-modeling-analysts</item>
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/learn/finance-for-non-finance</item>
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/learn/duke-behavioral-finance</item>
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/specializations/wharton-business-financial-modeling</item>
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/learn/finance-fundamentals</item>
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/learn/python-statistics-financial-analysis</item>
        <item name="smu">https://www.coursera.org/specializations/costaccounting</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_title">
        <item name="Financial Market">Introduction to Financial Markets</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">Introduction to Finance and Accounting</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">Investment and Portfolio Management</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">Finance &amp; Quantitatie Modelling for Analysts</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">Finance for Non-Finance Professionals</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">Behavioral Finance</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">Business and Financial Modelling</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">Fundamentals of Finance</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">Cost Accounting</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_host">
        <item name="Financial Market">Robert Shiller</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">Brian J Bushee</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">Arzu Ozoguz</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">Michael R Roberts</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">James Weston</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">Emma Rasiel</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">Sergei Savin</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">Marla Noel</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">Xuhu Wan</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">Gunther Friedl</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="courseHost_Desc">
        <item name="Financial Market">Professor of Economics, Yale University</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">The Geoffrey T. Boisi Professor</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">Finance Faculty</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">Professor of Finance, University of Pennsylvania</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">Harmon Whittington Professor of Finance</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">Associate Chair and Professor</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">Associate Professor of Operations, Information and Decisions</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">UCI Division of Continuing Education Instructor</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">Associate Professor</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">Prof. Dr.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_duration">
        <item name="Financial Market">34 hours</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">5 months</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">6 months</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">4 months</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">14 hours</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">5 hours</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">6 months</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">10 hours</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">13 hours</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">3 months</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_lesson">
        <item name="Financial Market">7 modules</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">4 courses</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">5 courses</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">4 courses</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">5 modules</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">3 modules</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">5 courses</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">4 modules</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">4 modules</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">3 courses</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_desc">
        <item name="Financial Market">An overview of the ideas, methods, and institutions that permit human society to manage risks and foster enterprise.  Emphasis on financially-savvy leadership skills. Description of practices today and analysis of prospects for the future. Introduction to risk management and behavioral finance principles to understand the real-world functioning of securities, insurance, and banking industries.  The ultimate goal of this course is using such industries effectively and towards a better society.</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">This specialization provides an introduction to corporate finance and accounting, emphasizing their application to a wide variety of real-world situations spanning personal finance, corporate decision-making, financial intermediation, and how accounting standards and managerial incentives affect the financial reporting process. It begins with concepts and applications like time value of money, risk-return tradeoff, retirement savings, mortgage financing, auto leasing, asset valuation, and many others.  The specialization uses Excel to make the experience more hands-on and help learners understand the concepts more directly.  From valuing claims and making financing decisions, to elements of a basic financial model, the coursework provides a solid foundation to corporate finance. The specialization then moves to financial accounting, enabling learners to read financial statements and to understand the language and grammar of accounting.  The coursework introduces bookkeeping fundamentals, accrual accounting, cash flow analysis, among much else!  Finally, using the foundational knowledge of accounting, the specialization teaches learners how to understand and analyze key information that companies provide in their statements, including types of assets and liabilities and longer-term investments and debts, and finally the difference between tax reporting and financial reporting.</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">In this four-course Specialization, you’ll learn the essential skills of portfolio management and personal investing. All investors – from the largest wealth funds to the smallest individual investors – share common issues in investing: how to meet their liabilities, how to decide where to invest, and how much risk to take on. In this Specialization, you will learn how to think about, discuss, and formulate solutions to these investment questions. You will learn the theory and the real-world skills necessary to design, execute, and evaluate investment proposals that meet financial objectives. You will begin with an overview of global financial markets and instruments that characterize the investment opportunities available to today’s investor. You will then learn how to construct optimal portfolios that manage risk effectively, and how to capitalize on understanding behavioral biases and irrational behavior in financial markets. You will learn the best practices in portfolio management and performance evaluation as well as current investment strategies. By the end of your Capstone Project, you will have mastered the analytical tools, quantitative skills, and practical knowledge necessary for long-term investment management success.</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">The role of an Analyst is dynamic, complex, and driven by a variety of skills. These skills range from a basic understanding of financial statement data and non-financial metrics that can be linked to financial performance, to a deeper dive into business and financial modeling. Analysts also utilize spreadsheet models, modeling techniques, and common investment analysis application as part of their toolkit to make informed financial decisions and investments. This multifaceted specialization will equip a learner who might be interested in entering the dynamic world of data and business analysis, and/or is interested gaining deeper technical knowledge in Finance and Quantitative Modeling. Starting from the fundamentals of quantitative modeling, you will learn how to put data to work by using spreadsheets and leverage spreadsheets as a powerful, accessible data analysis tool. You will also be introduced to the world of corporate finance, and gain a better understanding of finance fundamentals, including a variety of real-world situations spanning personal finance, corporate decision-making and financial intermediation.</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">This short course surveys all the major topics covered in a full semester MBA level finance course, but with a more intuitive approach on a very high conceptual level.  The goal here is give you a roadmap and framework for how financial professional make decisions. We will cover the basics of financial valuation, the time value of money, compounding returns, and discounting the future.  You will understand discounted cash flow (DCF) valuation and how it compares to other methods.  We also step inside the mind of a corporate financial manager and develop the basic tools of capital budgeting.  We will survey the how, when, and where to spend money, make tradeoffs about investment, growth, dividends, and how to ensure sound fiscal discipline.  Our journey then turns to a Wall Street or capital markets perspective of investments as we discuss the fundamental tradeoff between risk and return.  We then synthesize our discussion of risk with our valuation framework and incorporate it into series of direct applications to practice. This course requires no prior familiarity with finance.  Rather, it is intended to be a first step for anyone who is curious about understanding stock markets, valuation, or corporate finance.  We will walk through all of the tools and quantitative analysis together and develop a guide for understanding the seemingly complex decisions that finance professionals make. By the end of the course, you will develop an understanding of the major conceptual levers that push and pull on financial decision making and how they relate to other areas of business.  The course should also serve as a roadmap for where to further your finance education and it would be an excellent introduction of any students contemplating an MBA or Finance concentration, but who has little background in the area.</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">We make thousands of decisions every day. Do I cross the road now, or wait for the oncoming truck to pass? Should I eat fries or a salad for lunch? How much should I tip the cab driver? We usually make these decisions with almost no thought, using what psychologists call “heuristics” – rules of thumb that enable us to navigate our lives. Without these mental shortcuts, we would be paralyzed by the multitude of daily choices. But in certain circumstances, these shortcuts lead to predictable errors – predictable, that is, if we know what to watch out for. Did you know, for example, that we are naturally biased towards selling investments that are doing well for us, but holding on to those that are doing poorly? Or that we often select sub-optimal insurance payment plans, and routinely purchase insurance that we don’t even need? And why do so many of us fail to enroll in our employer’s corporate retirement plans, even when the employer offers to match our contributions? Behavioral finance is the study of these and dozens of other financial decision-making errors that can be avoided, if we are familiar with the biases that cause them. In this course, we examine these predictable errors, and discover where we are most susceptible to them. This course is intended to guide participants towards better financial choices. Learn how to improve your spending, saving, and investing decisions for the future.</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">Wharton\'s Business and Financial Modeling Specialization is designed to help you make informed business and financial decisions. These foundational courses will introduce you to spreadsheet models, modeling techniques, and common applications for investment analysis, company valuation, forecasting, and more. When you complete the Specialization, you\'ll be ready to use your own data to describe realities, build scenarios, and predict performance. </item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">Welcome to Fundamentals of Finance. This 4 module course will help you understand and affect the performance of your unit or organization’s profitability. By the end of this course, you will be able to implement finance and accounting concepts to drive your organization\'s growth, analyze financial statements and understand the factors in productivity and profitability, and create forecasting and budgeting. You will also have the ability to evaluate and manage cash flow, implement strategies around financing, and use of ratios in running a business.</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">Course Overview: https://youtu.be/JgFV5qzAYno Python is now becoming the number 1 programming language for data science. Due to python’s simplicity and high readability, it is gaining its importance in the financial industry.  The course combines both python coding and statistical concepts and applies into analyzing financial data, such as stock data. By the end of the course, you can achieve the following using python: \n\n- Import, pre-process, save and visualize financial data into pandas Dataframe \n\n- Manipulate the existing financial data by generating new variables using multiple columns \n\n- Recall and apply the important statistical concepts (random variable, frequency, distribution, population and sample, confidence interval, linear regression, etc. ) into financial contexts \n\n- Build a trading model using multiple linear regression model \n\n- Evaluate the performance of the trading model using different investment indicators \n\nJupyter Notebook environment is configured in the course platform for practicing python coding without installing any client applications.</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">View the Specialization trailer: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XE5Rx91bdYw \n\nMany corporate decisions need cost accounting information. When you know the costs of your products, you will make better pricing decisions and you can better choose which products to offer. When you know the costs of your departments, you can better detect inefficiencies and you can better incentivize your employees. \n\nIn this Specialization, you will learn the fundamentals of cost accounting. Three courses cover the basics of cost accounting. We will start with an introduction to product costing. How can you figure out the costs of your individual products? Next, we will discuss how to connect cost information with revenue information to calculate profits and profitability. Finally, we focus on how to use the information provided by cost accounting systems to optimize your business decisions. \n\nWe have created the courses of this Specialization for interdisciplinary young professionals seeking to develop cost accounting skills. At the same time, the courses can help students in management and business administration to repeat the content of their introductory cost accounting course.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_university">
        <item name="Financial Market">Yale University</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">University of Pennsylvania</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">Rice University</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">Rice University</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">Rice University</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">Duke University</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">University of Pennsylvania</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">University of California, Irvine</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">Technische Universitat Munchen (TUM)</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_universityDesc">
        <item name="Financial Market">7 modules</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">4 courses</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">5 courses</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">4 courses</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">5 modules</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">3 modules</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">5 courses</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">4 modules</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">4 modules</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">3 courses</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="course_publishedDates">
        <item name="Financial Market">20 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Introduction to Finance and Accounting">21 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Investment and Portfolio Management">22 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Finance &amp; Quantitative Modelling for Analysts">23 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Finance for Non-Finance Professionals">24 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Behavioral Finance">25 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Business and Financial Modelling">26 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Fundamentals of Finance">27 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Python and Statistic for Financial Analysis">28 December 2022</item>
        <item name="Cost Accounting">29 December 2022</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>

    <!--    Even though students are exposed to basic financial literacy concepts such as “Budgeting”, youths do not put it into practice as the modules only provide theoretical knowledge, not practical knowledge.-->

    <!--    LearnLoop aims to provide the practical knowledge aspect through features such as:\n ⚪ Setting Budgets\n ⚪ Budgeting\n ⚪ Expenditure Tracker\n ⚪ Financial Literacy Courses\n ⚪ Student Discount Library-->